Explore Paradise
Guava Island is a comedy, thriller, music film directed by Hiro Murai.
Deni Maroon, a musician and dock worker is determined to pull off a music
festival against the interests of the local factory owner.
Deni Maroon, played by Donald Glover.
Kofi Novia, played by Rihanna.
Yara Love, played by Letitia Wright.
Red Cargo, played by Nonso Anozie.
Kito, played by Alan Jael Velázquez Abreu.
Butcher, played by Renny Arozarena.
Guava Island is a 2019 American musical film directed by Hiro Murai (his feature directorial debut) with a screenplay
by Stephen Glover and story by Donald Glover, Stephen Glover, Ibra Ake, Jamal Olori and Fam Udeorji.
It stars Donald Glover and Rihanna in the lead roles of Deni and Kofi, respectively,
and was first exhibited at the Coachella Festival on April 11, 2019.
It was then released on April 13, 2019, by Amazon Studios through Amazon Prime Video for anyone to watch
without a subscription for 18 hours before being available to Prime subscribers only.
In the final hour of the 18 hours, the film was streamed
on the Coachella YouTube page and Twitch.
Donald Glover was co-headlining at the event as
Childish Gambino (his stage name).
The film explores themes of musician, music
festival, animated scene, dockworker.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.